<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Berkant AYDIN</title><link href="http://berkantaydin.com.tr/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://berkantaydin.com.tr/feeds/all-en.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://berkantaydin.com.tr/</id><updated>2014-02-27T09:37:00+02:00</updated><entry><title>Ramsay GORDON</title><link href="http://berkantaydin.com.tr/ramsay%20gordon.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-02-27T09:37:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Berkant AYDIN</name></author><id>tag:berkantaydin.com.tr,2014-02-27:ramsay gordon.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I got a Netflix ID. Because i have to improve my English speaking and understanding skills. I really need this because i hate to read subtitles. Because it's very boring while watching TV. You can't see any mimics and other visual things. When i surfing in first time at Netflix, i saw &lt;em&gt;Ramsey GORDON: Kitchen Nightmares&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I watched him before at Hell's Kitchen and other TV programs. I really love him because i think he is very good chief and his comminication skills is simple and best for us. He know your job and his job is my favorite. I really like him. I will keep watcing Ramsey GORDON. I will f**king watch!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...and some words from Ramsey...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This duck is too raw. I still hear its sound&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary><category term="cook"></category><category term="ramsey gordon"></category></entry><entry><title>His name is Farter</title><link href="http://berkantaydin.com.tr/his-name-is-farter.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-02-19T19:45:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Berkant AYDIN</name></author><id>tag:berkantaydin.com.tr,2014-02-19:his-name-is-farter.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Farter is my cat. My cousin found him while wait me front of the Burger King. After i took the vet. for general medical control and some vaccines. He was very small when we found. We don't understand it is a male or female. We and vet. think, it is a female but i understand it is not female two months later.
He haven't any name for two months because we didn't choose any names for it. Still, we didn't give any names understand his gender.
Someday we discovered a thing. If you too much love our cat than will be fart. Whaat!? Yea, i know it, this is very awkward but true. Whenever love it, he will fart again! Ok, we are understand this problem and i give a name, like Porter from Payback movie. His name is Farter!&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="pets"></category><category term="cats"></category><category term="farter"></category></entry><entry><title>Pelican ile yeni bir başlangıç</title><link href="http://berkantaydin.com.tr/blog-with-pelican.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-01-23T19:45:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Berkant AYDIN</name></author><id>tag:berkantaydin.com.tr,2014-01-23:blog-with-pelican.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;İlk blog yazımı kısa tutacağım zira şu anda teknik bir kaç test yapmaktayım. Bu yapıyı oluşturmada bana en çok yardımı &lt;a href="http://blog.mathieu-leplatre.info/publish-your-pelican-blog-on-github-pages-via-travis-ci.html"&gt;Mathieu Leplatre&lt;/a&gt; sağlamıştır. Teşekkürlerimi sunuyorum.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="pelican"></category><category term="static site generator"></category><category term="python"></category></entry></feed>